Don't be afraid.
I'm God, you see!
What is that thing?
And this smell...
God my ass!
You said you wouldn't do any—
You runaway brat.
You ignorant fools!
The great principle of capitalism is give-and-take.
There's no such thing as give-and-give!
I am God.
Love is me.
Don't act on your own.
You came looking for love,
and yet you reject me?
Sorry.
I physically can't stand his looks or his smell.
It's always hard to understand how you girls think.
But we agree on that, at least.
Come to me.
I know you haven't gone far.
Even back then, you only went
one subway stop from home.
You got scared and ran back home,
but there was no place for you, was there?
Your parents don't love you.
I'm the only one who will.
When you ran away, weren't you saved for a moment?
That was blowing off steam.
That's the kind of relationship you should have built.
You must understand.
Let's blow off each other's steam.
I'll blow it off for you.
I'm going
to blow your mind.
My...
Oh, wow!
But why's his mind down there?
Nothing I eat will taste right for a while.
Thank you.
I didn't do it for you.
Give-and-give would just be gross.
I guess so.
But it made me happy.
Having somebody protect me.
Is that so?
We're a little late.
This place is hard to find.
Not so loud.
You got lost?
No.
Oh, here.
For you.
Thanks.
Come in! It's cramped, though.
Excuse us!
I'm Aonuma Neiru.
Oh, my, how polite.
Hi, Ai's Mom.
My.
Hello.
Oh, my! Aren't you Mr. Sawaki's...
Sawaki Momoe. I'm his niece.
What a pretty young lady.
Th—
Hey, do you have that cake?
Lay out Neiru's snacks, too.
Fine, fine.
You have so many friends.
Isn't that great, Ai?
Hey!
Please, please, please!
You really are shameless.
You haven't even finished yours.
Stingy.
Now, now.
Still, you're really my uncle's student, Ai?
I hear he's crazy popular with the girls at school.
Makes sense.
If you were a guy, I'd want to date you.
Stop that.
I think Koito liked Mr. Sawaki, too.
Who's Koito?
The girl Ai's trying to save.
Oh, I see.
Oh.
I just had a crazy idea.
What? What is it?
Okay, I'll tell you.
Maybe Ai's best friend Koito
was actually dating Mr. Sawaki.
Then, something terrible happened, and...
Oh? Do you have company?
W-Wait a minute!
We do.
Ai's friends are here!
My uncle's not like that.
He's so nice that he adopts lots of rescue cats.
Maybe he just likes cats.
He might have a dark side.
Yeah!
A teacher got hands on with a student,
and when it got dicey, bam!
Just like that.
There's no way.
Maybe she got pregnant.
Pregnant?!
Pregnant.
Yeah, pregnant.
Give it a rest!
S-Sorry.
I was kidding.
Sorry.
I really don't know why Koito died.
So...
Why not ask your mom?
Maybe Mr. Sawaki told her something.
Hey, maybe he only checks on you every week
because he thinks you've got some kind of proof.
That could be it, right?
I can't ask.
My mom really trusts Mr. Sawaki,
and I'm always making her worry.
And she stopped asking about my injuries
after I clammed up about them.
"Clammed," huh?
What?
You got allergies?
No, it's just that I can picture Ai as a clam.
I-I mean...
But if you tell her you're going out to fight in your sleep,
you'll just worry her more.
She might think you're on something.
She'd never believe you.
Yes.
That's why we can't tell anyone.
It's our story that no one else knows about, right?
A story... that no one knows about.
Momoe's here?
Yes, I recognized her because she looks like you.
They're in different schools. Where did they meet?
There's no reason to have a complex.
Your eyes are charming.
Okay.
I'll paint how you look to me.
When it's finished, I want you to have confidence.
Me, confident?
I hear Mr. Sawaki's entering it in the next exhibition.
He says he wants to win a prize
and make a living as a painter.
A painting of me?
Confident?
If not, you should decline.
Mr. Sawaki's future is on the line.
I...
I wish my mom was more like yours, Ai.
Why? What's yours like?
Mine's toxic and awful.
I bet when I was born and first saw her face, I thought,
"This lady wants to stay a woman her
whole life and never be a parent."
"Oh, no! What do I do?"
It's your turn, Rika.
My mom always does everything
perfectly, at work and at home.
She works really hard.
But I think that's probably why my dad left.
Lots of guys are proud.
A capable woman actually spoils them.
Why are you looking at me?
Because it's your turn.
You're an anachronistic fool.
Who are you calling "fool"?
Stop, fool.
Coochy-coochy-coo...
How about here?
They really get along, huh?
Yeah.
No, we—
What about this spot?
Hey, do you do hair treatments?
It looks like you've got some damage.
Don't touch me.
I want to be free. Don't tie me down.
Oh, who cares?
Hey, isn't my hair pretty?
Not a single split end.
I'm at my prettiest now.
Nothing can replace youth.
Not interested.
Aren't you going to ask? About why I died?
I just complete my objectives.
Get back!
Girls become adults.
The miraculous beauty of a butterfly emerging.
A brief moment.
A moment of shocking beauty when its
transience is powerfully reflected.
Mirror, mirror on the wall,
who's the fairest of them all?
Soon, beauty fades.
My mom's just a sow.
No amount of liposuction or hyaluronic acid
will ever stop her aging.
In fact, her attempts to stop it
are unbelievably ugly on their own.
You're pretty, too.
Why don't you die?
Why not die when you're at your most beautiful?
This isn't good.
Why cling to a meaningless life?
Mirror, mirror on the wall,
How do I beat them?
who's the fairest of them all?
Hey, why don't you die?
Mirror, mirror on the wall, who's the fairest of them all?
Why don't you?
Tell me!
Who?
Okay, coast's clear.
The crosswalk is right there.
Who wants to wait?
You have a lot, huh, Momo?
Yeah, a bunch, actually.
Be quiet, Rika.
Yay!
Ai!
Hey, there's an echo.
I wonder what they grew here.
That reminds me; I'm starving.
About six times, I think.
Is six times a lot or a little?
Who knows?
Then...
All girls.
They all seriously say they love me. It's a pain.
Admiration, maybe?
Like with Takarazuka?
Yeah.
But you don't like it, right, Momo?
God sure is cruel.
Outside food and drink are prohibited.
More importantly, buy your Eggs and leave.
Come on, let us play one game.
This is basically a kind of group therapy.
Yeah, to let us feel that we're not alone.
We might kill ourselves without it.
Just one game.
Yes!
I couldn't even reach the pins before.
I'm getting buff.
Thank God for Eggs.
Your turn, Momoe.
Okay.
Whoa.
It's like a date photo.
All my photos with girls come out like that.
I'll save it.
See?
Wow, you're right.
Oh, this picture's cute.
Haruka took this one for me.
Haruka was willing to see me as a girl.
Your friend who killed herself?
Yeah.
But she suddenly took her clothes off in the infirmary.
She put the moves on you? Whoa.
I got scared and ended up pushing her away.
I get that.
You don't expect it to come from a girl who's your friend.
I got chills! I was shaking!
What should I have done?
Well, let's drop the gloomy talk.
There are lots of other games.
Let's play our hearts out.
Yeah, let's!
What do you mean?
You promised you'd only play one game.
Come on!
Buy Eggs.
This place is—
Ura-Acca!
Where's the harm?
Play well, fight well.
What's that, Ai?
You don't completely hate being popular, do you?
Even with girls?
Well, I guess I care about the girls
who follow me on Insta and things.
You're half-hearted.
Sometimes you end up enjoying something
even though you didn't mean to.
Really?
I did it!
Damn it!
Maybe so.
I couldn't beat you even once.
Games like that are kind of my thing.
A gamer? You secretly a nerd?
That was a first.
Same for me.
That's normal, isn't it?
You're totally a nerd.
You've had your fun.
Now, buy your Eggs, go home, and go to sleep.
What? I don't wanna leave.
I'm having the time of my life.
Yeah, I haven't had this much fun in ages.
Good grief. It's your fault for spoiling them.
Oh, yeah; Neiru, can I have your contact info?
I'm not spoiling them; soldiers need their rest.
Yes. Tell me yours, too.
Too much rest will make them slack off like you do.
Oh, sure.
Here's mine.
You're so uptight.
How about we just stop buying Eggs?
Huh?
Now that I think about it, Chiemi went and died on her own.
It might be true that I was the reason,
but dying isn't playing fair.
Do I have to feel so responsible?
Seriously?
It's true, isn't it?
I knew it. What Ai saw was just an act.
No!
I'm a woman, so I get swept away
by my emotions in the moment.
Hey, Rika...
What about you, Momoe?
Huh?
Are you responsible?
Of course you feel guilty. So do I.
But should we really feel so
responsible that we'd risk our own lives?
Well...
Rika...
stop it already.
Especially you, Ai.
She died without even talking to you.
That's not your fault.
So, why do you have to go fight?
Because I want to know the truth about why Koito died.
That curiosity could get you killed!
My parents are one thing, but you've got a great mom.
You want to make her sad?!
You don't even know if Koito wants
to come back to life in the first place!
That's not...
What, did Koito's statue tell you she wants to come back?
Why would you say that?!
Rika, stop it—
Someone has to be the bad guy!
If you want friends, you've got 'em!
Sorry, but I'm going.
I don't want to go, but I have to.
What for?!
For someone selfish enough to... kill themselves...
Rika, Neiru's trying to save her sister.
Wrong.
Wrong about what?
My sister stabbed me.
Huh?
Then, she ran away and jumped off a bridge.
That's...
That's what they told me when I woke up in the ICU.
Then you've got even less of a reason.
The scar aches and keeps me awake.
But the pain has faded since I started going there.
When I try to forget her, my scar aches, like a curse.
That's why I go.
No other reason.
It's for me.
You don't have to go if you don't want to.
Guilt and curiosity fade.
Sooner or later, you'll forget 'em.
It's fine. You don't have to go.
Good, right?
I mean,
that's just adolescence.
Beauty is a momentary season of metamorphosis.
Mirror, mirror on the wall, who's the fairest of them all?
Dying is the same.
Killing your own beautiful body is another metamorphosis.
Getting old and ugly or trying
to resist aging are both comedy.
There must be a real one.
Just comedy!
Who is it?
Who?
I'm going to blow your mind.
How did you...
I didn't.
You just got on my nerves.
You actually regret it, right?
After all, no one will call you pretty ever again.
"Why don't I die," huh?
You tempted me to die, didn't you?
Well done.
Teenage rebellion.
They'll want to go if we say not to.
They know that doing that will build up their own identities.
Ai, lend me money.
I'm out.
You're kidding.
To be continued.